<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!-- THIS FILE WAS AUTOMATICALLY GENERATED BY ContestGen AT Mon Nov 26 13:56:38 GMT+03:00 2001 -->
<problem id='d'>
<testers>
  <acm-tester
    tests        = '16'
    inputs       = 'wall.{test##}'
    answers      = 'wall.{test##}a'
    input-names  = 'wall.in'
    output-names = 'wall.out'
    time-limit   = '5s'
  >
    <checker
       class     = 'pcms2.testlib.Checker'
       program   = '!wall.exe'
       command   = '{exec:!/!.!} {input} {output} {answer} result.xml -appes'
       exec-id   = 'bin.x86.exe.win32'
       result    = 'result.xml'
    />
  </acm-tester>
</testers>

<statement>
<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
<title>Wall</title>
</head>
<body>

<h2>Wall</h2>

<table>
<tr><td colspan="1" rowspan="1"><strong>Input file</strong></td><td colspan="1" rowspan="1"><tt>wall.in</tt></td></tr>
<tr><td colspan="1" rowspan="1"><strong>Output file</strong></td><td colspan="1" rowspan="1"><tt>wall.out</tt></td></tr>
</table>

<p><img alt="Sample wall picture" src="wall.gif" style="float:right"></img>
Once upon a time there was a greedy King who ordered his
chief Architect to build a wall around King's castle. The
King was so greedy, that he would not listen to his Architect's 
proposals to build a beautiful brick wall with a perfect shape
and nice tall towers. Instead, he ordered to build the wall 
around the whole castle using the least amount of stone and
labor, but demanded that the wall should not come closer to
the castle than a certain distance. If the King finds that
the Architect has used more resources to build the wall than
it was absolutely necessary to satisfy those requirements,
then the Architect will loose his head. Moreover, he demanded
Architect to introduce at once a plan of the wall listing
the exact amount of resources that are needed to build
the wall.</p>

<p>Your task is to help poor Architect to save his head, 
by writing a program that will find the minimum possible
length of the wall that he could build around the
castle to satisfy King's requirements.</p>

<p>The task somewhat simplified by the fact, that King's
castle has polygonal shape and is situated on a flat ground.
Architect has already established a Cartesian coordinate 
system and has precisely measured the coordinates of
castle's vertices in feet.</p>

<h3>Input</h3>

<p>The first line of the input file contains two integer 
numbers N and L separated by a space.
N (3 &#8804; N &#8804; 1000) is the number of vertices in the King's
castle, and L (1 &#8804; L &#8804; 1000) is the minimal number 
of feet that King allows for the wall to come close to
the castle.</p>

<p>Next N lines describe coordinates of castle's vertices in
a clockwise order. Each line contains two integer numbers
X<sub>i</sub> and Y<sub>i</sub> separated by a space 
(-10000 &#8804; X<sub>i</sub>, Y<sub>i</sub> &#8804; 10000)
that represent coordinates of i<sup>th</sup> vertex.
All vertices are different and the sides of the castle do
not intersect anywhere except for vertices.</p>

<h3>Output</h3>

<p>Write to the output file the single number that represents
the minimal possible length of the wall in feet that could be
built around the castle to satisfy King's requirements.
You must present the integer number of feet to the King,
because the floating numbers are not invented yet. However,
you must round the result in such a way, that it is
accurate to 8 inches (1 foot is equal to 12 inches),
since the King will not tolerate larger error in
the estimates.</p>

<h3>Sample input</h3>

<pre xml:space="preserve"><tt>9 100
200 400
300 400
300 300
400 300
400 400
500 400
500 200
350 200
200 200</tt></pre>

<h3>Output for the sample input</h3>

<pre xml:space="preserve"><tt>1628</tt></pre>

</body>
</html>
</statement>
</problem>
